Officially founding the University of Loquntia, just in time to start discontinuing classes?
<br>
11 JUN 2015
<p>
The Library of Blue Ink has, since 2011 offered classes in the constructed language Loqunta (also known originally as <i><font face="Times New Roman">Бoxobhvath</font></i>, <i><font face="Times New Roman">Otcy/Иtcy</font></i>, and <i><font face="Times New Roman">Иxиpϙaex</font></i> for you <i><font face="Times New Roman">Иxиpϙaexия oϙϣapabиpab</font></i>) for all those who wished to learn a quirky made-up language. After having at total of 2 students in the recent 4 years, it has been decided that courses L02BB1, L02BB2, L02BB3, and L02BB4 will no longer be offered. Students who have received certificates or transcripts which appreciate their studies in Loqunta will still be honoured by the University of Loquntia. 

Fans of Loqunta need not fret, if they found the language F'shanka enough, there may be a Loqunta revival and everyone will have <i><font face="Times New Roman">hpabp ataѳoϭϫ Иxиpϙaexия aкhиԓѳия oϙ</font></i> back, but it may take a team effort, because there are few old souls who can speak even a lick of Loqunta.